The Peter Bekker Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Peter Bekker, Jr.
  - Subseries 1.8 Audio Recordings, Cassettes are organized alphabetically
    - Subseries 1.8.1 Cassettes
      - [Harlow, Gloria] Gloria Harlow #1 "I wanna new drug"--- Tammy Bakker Gloria Harlow/Q-Z00/Tampa Bay, Artist: Gloria Harlow Length: 00:01:22 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.35.mp3, 1.8.1.12.35.wav (Box 12, Cassette 35)
      - [Harlow, Gloria] Gloria Harlow #2 "Anything Butt Naked" July 31, 1987 Gloria Harlow and Carl Perkins Q-z00/Q-105/Tampa Bay, Artist: Gloria Harlow Length: 00:04:09 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.36.mp3, 1.8.1.12.36.wav (Box 12, Cassette 36)
      - [Harris, EmmyLou]Emmy Lou / Brand New Dance Blue Bird Brand New Dance: Wheels love, tougher than the rest, in his world, sweet dreams of you, easy for you to say, rollin + ramblin, better off w/out you, never be anyone else but you, brand new dance, red red rose Bluebird: heaven only knows, you've been on my mind, Icy blue heart, Love is, No regrets, Lonely street, Heart break hill, I still miss someone, A river for him, If you were a bluebird, Artist: Emmy Lou Harris Length: 01:29:21 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.37.mp3, 1.8.1.12.37.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 37)
      - [Harris, EmmyLou] Emmy Lou Harris Cougar's Prayer/ Roses in the show\ Side A: Cougars Prayer: A ways to go - the light - High powered love - you don’t know me - payer in open D - Crescent city - Lovin' you again - Jersulaem tomorrow - thanks to you - I hear a call - Ballad g - A runaway house \ Side B: Roses in the snow: Roses in the snow - way faring stranger - green pastures - the boxer - darkest hour - Ill go steppin too - youre learning - Jardan- Miss the Mississippi and you - Gold watch and chain, Artist: Emmy Lou Harris Length: 01:29:31 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.38.mp3 1.8.1.12.38.wav See folder for 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 38)
      - [Harris, EmmyLou] Emmy Lou Harris Till Tuesday/ Welcome Home, Artist: Emmy Lou Harris Length: 01:15:53 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.39.mp3, 1.8.1.12.39.wav (Box 12, Cassette 39)
      - [Harrison, George] Beatles Interview 6, Artist: George Harrison Length: 01:32:42 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.11.18.mp3, 1.8.1.11.18.wav (Box 11, Cassette 18)
        Interview with the Beatles
      - [Hay, Colin] Colin Hay Interview "Men @ Work" NYC, Artist: Colin Hay Length: 00:44:00 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.40.mp3, 1.8.1.12.40.wav (Box 12, Cassette 40)
      - [Hauptman, Harvey] Blackout 77 WCBS Radio Capsule digest. Harvey Haupptman, anchor, Artist: Harvey Hauptmann Length: 00:31:41 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.41.mp3, 1.8.1.12.41.wav (Box 12, Cassette 41)
      - [Hendry, Nona] Gene Simmons /Nona Hendry x Blotto /Alabama, Artist: Nona Hendry Length: 01:24:43 Type: Interview File Names: 1.7.1.11.2.mp3, 1.7.1.11.2.wav (Box 11, Cassette 2)
      - [Hicks, Dan] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, 1:26:54; Artist: Dan Hicks Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Hodges, John] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, 1:26:54; Artist: John Hodges Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Jackson, Janet] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, 1:26:54; Artist: Janet Jackson Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Jackson, Michael] How. Bloom, Artist: Michael Jackson Length: 00:31:58 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.42.mp3, 1.8.12.42.wav (Box 12, Cassette 42)
      - [Jaluka] Jaluka/ Scatterlings \ K+A McGarrigle, Artist: Jaluka Length: 01:27:31 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.43.mp3, 1.8.1.12.43.wav (Box 12, Cassette 43)
      - [James, Bob] J.P. Rameau / B. James, Artist: Bob James Length: Unknown Type: Unknown Note: Cassette does not play (Box 12, Cassette 44)
      - [Johnson, Horace and the Tractors] Horace Johnson & The Tractors Dance Medley-14:32 normal eq-no dolby Peter Bekker The Fleet Street Group 184 bleecker, ny 10012. 254-3177 Driver- Gay Corporation man- My phone is so hot- Swingers in cabs- Jane Fonda. (dance medley). Normal eq-no dolby-14:32, Artist: Horace Johnson and the Tractors Length: 00:15:12 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.1.mp3, 1.8.1.13.1.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 1)
      - [Johnson, Horace and the Tractors] Horace Johnson & The Tractors Side A: 1) basic trax (5) 8-9-80 2) Vocal overdubs (5) 9-19-80 Side B: 3) Sax overdubs (5) 9-23-80 4) final mix (5) 10-3-80 Unique NYC, Artist: Horace Johnson and the Tractors Length: 00:29:01 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.2.mp3, 1.8.1.13.2.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 2)
      - [Jones, Rickie Lee] Rickie Lee/ The Magazine /Scandal, Artist: Rickie Lee Jones Length: 01:31:24 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.3.mp3, 1.8.1.13.3.wav (Box 13, Cassette 3)
      - [Kiddo] Lena Lovich 4/13/83 epic la Simple minds 4/15 a&m la Kiddo 4/15/83 a&m la Whispers 4/15 elektra la, Artist: Kiddo Length: 01:40:29 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.12.26.mp3, 1.8.1.12.26.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 26)
      - [King Sunny Ade] UB40 - Jeff Morgan King Sunny Ade, Artist: King Sunny Ade Length: 0:21:56 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.4.mp3, 1.8.1.13.4.wav (Box 13, Cassette 4)
      - [KCLC] Sex- Plane Trip KCLC-FM News, Artist: KCLC Length: 00:21:56 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.5.mp3, 1.8.1.13.5.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 5)
      - [KCLC Radio] KCLC- Promos, Artist: KCLC Length: 00:21:48 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.6.mp3, 1.8.1.13.6.wav (Box 13, Cassette 6)
      - [KDFW Radio] Dallas Nurse \ KDFW freedom of info CLORISE TINSLEY- LARRY BOFF / BILLIE MYRICk-DENNIS FLEMING, Artist: KDFW Length: 00:03:07 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.7.mp3, 1.8.1.13.7.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 7)
      - [KMOX Radio] American Dream Deferred: Poverty in the St. Louis Area KMOX Radio, St. Louis, MO, Artist: KMOX Length: 00:29:53 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.8.mp3, 1.8.1.13.8.wav (Box 13, Cassette 8)
      - [KMOX Radio] A President Resigns August 8, 1974 President Nixon Resigns Vice-President For Comments President Nixon's Goodbye Gerald Ford- 38th President of the United States Narrated by Bob Hardy Historic Events as Broadcast by KMOX/1120 CBS RADIO "the Voice Of St. Louis", Artist: KMOX Length: 01:05:05 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.9.mp3, 1.8.1.13.9.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 9)
      - [KNX]Sounders for KNX Peter Bekker, 9/82, Artist: KNX Length: 00:08:37 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.10.mp3, 1.8.1.13.10.wav (Box 13, Cassette 10)
      - [Ladysmith Black Mambazo] Ladysmith- Shaka Zulu Morrison/Chieftans- Irish Heart \ B: Morrison-Chieftans Star of The County Down/Irish Heartbeat/ TAMO Chleamhnas Deanta/ Raglanroaa/ She Moved The The Fair/ I'll Tell Me Ma/ Carrickfergus/ Celtic Ray/ My Lagan Love/ Maries Wedding \ A: Ladysmith- Unomathemba/ Hello My Baby/ At Golgotha/ King of Kings/ The Earth Is Never Satisfied/ How Long?/ Home of the Heroes/ These Are The Guys/ Rain, Rain Beautiful Rain? Who Were U Talking To?, Artist: Ladysmith Length: 01:27:34 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.6.mp3, 1.8.1.12.6.wav (Box 12, Cassette 6)
      - [Ladysmith Black Mambazo] Lady Smith-Shaka Zulu Earthworks-Various, Artist: Ladysmith Length: 01:25:47 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.12.mp3, 1.8.1.13.12.wav (Box 13, Cassette 12)
      - [Lamb, Bill] Bill Lamb 6/23/83 wb-Nashville\ Pam Tillis 6/23/83 WB- Nashville, Artist: Bill Lamb Length: 01:20:41 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.13.mp3, 1.8.1.13.13.wav (Box 13, Cassette 13)
      - [Lee, Brenda] DC 5/Ventures/Brenda Lee, Artist: Brenda Lee Length: 00:46:16 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.19.mp3, 1.8.1.12.19.wav (Box 12, Cassette 19)
      - [Lecher, Tom] Tom Lecher (Faves), Artist: Tom Lecher Length: 00:42:11 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.14.mp3, 1.8.1.13.14.wav (Box 13, Cassette 14)
      - [London Philharmonic] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, Artist: London Philharmonic Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Lovett, Lyle] Paul Simon - Rhythm of the Saints \Lyle Lovett\ Side a: The obvious child - cant run the but the coast - further to fly - she moves on - Born the right time - The cool cool river spirit voices - Rhythm of the saints \Side b: If I had a boat - Give back my heart - I loved you yesterday - Walk thru the broken land - LA County - She's no lady - Money - Black + Blue - Simple Song - Pontiac - Shes Hot to Go, Artist: Lyle Lovett Length: 01:23:51 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.15.mp3, 1.8.1.13.15.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 15)
      - [Lovich, Lena] Lena Lovich 4/13/83 epic la Simple minds 4/15 a&m la Kiddo 4/15/83 a&m la Whispers 4/15 elektra la, Artist: Lena Lovich Length: 01:40:29 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.12.26.mp3, 1.8.1.12.26.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 26)
      - [Manilow, Barry] WJOY-BVT: Between/Lines Manilow. Syracuse U. Prof. Marvin Druger with 2 Australian air traffic controllers, Artist: Barry Manilow Length: 00:52:41 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.29.mp3, 1.8.1.11.29.wav (Box 11, Cassette 29)
      - [Manilow, Barry] Between the Lines: Barry Manilow 1-10, 11-20, Artist: Barry Manilow Length: 01:35:37 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.30.mp3, 1.8.1.11.30.wav (Box 11, Cassette 30)
      - [Manilow, Barry] Interview Barry Manilow #1 Manilow 1 Manilow 2, 1:05:55; Artist: Barry Manilow Length: 01:05;55 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.31.mp3, 1.8.1.11.31.wav (Box 11, Cassette 31)
      - [Manilow, Barry] Interview Barry Manilow #3 Manilow 3 Manilow 4, 0:45:07; Artist: Barry Manilow Length: 00:45:07 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.32.mp3, 1.8.1.11.32.wav (Box 11, Cassette 32)
      - [Marley, Bob] Bob Marley- Sailor, Artist: Bob Marley Note: Tape does not play (Box 13, Cassette 16)
      - [Marley, Bob] Bob Marley - Sailor \ Essex House NYC\ 9/24/80 Itome, Artist: Bob Marley Note: Tape does not play (Box 13, Cassette 17)
      - [Martin, John] Ventures/John Martin, Artist: John Martin Length: 00:41:17 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.18.mp3, 1.8.1.13.18.wav (Box 13, Cassette 18)
      - [The McGarrigle Sisters] Jaluka/ Scatterlings \ K+A McGarrigle, Artist: Jaluka Length: 01:27:31 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.43.mp3, 1.8.1.12.43.wav (Box 12, Cassette 43)
      - [McKennit, Lorena] Lorena McKennit Altan \The Mask/Mirror- The Mystic Dream/The Bonny Swans/The Dark Night and Dark Souls/Marrakesh Night Marbos/Full Circle/Santiago/ The 2 Trees \Propsero's Speech- Tommy PeoplesThe Windmill/BeidgOyn, Artist: Lorena McKennit Length: 01.43.07 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.3.mp3, 1.8.1.11.3.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 3)
      - [McKennit, Lorena] Lorena McKennit/ The Visit/ Bonnie Raitt/Longing In Their Hearts \ A: All Souls Night/Bonny Portmore/Between The Shadows/Lady of Shalott/Greensleeves/Tango To Evora/Covetrard Lullaby/The Old Ways/Cymbeline \B: Love Sneaking Upon You/Longing In Their Hearts/ You/ Cool, Clear Water/Circle Dance/I sho Do/Dimming The Day/Feeling of Falling/Steal Your hEart Away/Storm Warning/ Hell To Pay/Shadow and Doubt, Artist: Lorena McKennit Length: 01:43:07 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.19.mp3, 1.8.1.13.19.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.16 for cassette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 19)
      - [McShann, Jay] Jay McShann Hootie Blues + confessin the blues, Artist: Jay McShann Length: 00:15:30 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.20.mp3, 1.8.1.13.20.wav (Box 13, Cassette 20)
      - [Men at Work] Colin Hay Interview "Men @ Work" NYC, Artist: Men at Work Length: 00:44:00 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.12.40.mp3, 1.8.1.12.40.wav (Box 12, Cassette 40)
      - [Men At Work] Someday/Someway Various \ Men @ work various, 1:03:11; Artist: Men at Work Length: 01:03:11 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.18.mp3, 1.8.12.18.wav (Box 12, Cassette 18)
      - [Mitchell, John] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, Artist: John Mitchell Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Mitchell, Rick] Rick Mitchell: Love's Gonna Get You/Kamikaze Lover/Squeeze it (to the last drop), Artist: Rick Mitchell Length: 00:11:03 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.21.mp3, 1.8.1.13.21.wav Note: 3 copies (Box 13, Cassette 21)
      - [Mitchell, Rick] Rick Mitchell - Demo Normal 29/bias Love's gunna get you - Kamikaze Lover- Squeeze it (to the last drop), Artist: Rick Mitchell Length: 00:10:32 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.22.mp3, 1.8.1.13.22.wav Note: 5 copies. See folder 1.8.1.6.16 for J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 22)
      - [Morgan, Jeffrey] UB40 - Jeff Morgan King Sunny Ade, Artist: King Sunny Ade Length: 0:21:56 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.4.mp3, 1.8.1.13.4.wav (Box 13, Cassette 4)
      - [Morrison, Van] Ladysmith- Shaka Zulu Morrison/Chieftans- Irish Heart \ B: Morrison-Chieftans Star of The County Down/Irish Heartbeat/ TAMO Chleamhnas Deanta/ Raglanroaa/ She Moved The The Fair/ I'll Tell Me Ma/ Carrickfergus/ Celtic Ray/ My Lagan Love/ Maries Wedding \ A: Ladysmith- Unomathemba/ Hello My Baby/ At Golgotha/ King of Kings/ The Earth Is Never Satisfied/ How Long?/ Home of the Heroes/ These Are The Guys/ Rain, Rain Beautiful Rain? Who Were U Talking To?, Artist: Van Morrison Length: 01:27:34 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.6.mp3, 1.8.1.12.6.wav (Box 12, Cassette 6)
      - [Music Sampler] MCAs New Music Sampler: Side A: The Fixx/"Are we ourselves?", Camelleons-UK/"Up the down escalator", Way of the west/"City for lovers", Men without Hats/"Where Do The Boys Go". Temper/"No Favors", Robit Hairman/"Africa's on Fire", Pukka Orchestra/"Listen To The Radio", Joe Ely/"Whats Shakin' Tonight", Real Life/"Send me an angel" Side B: Nik Kershaw/ "Wouldn't it be good", What is This/"My mind have still I", Tracey Ullman/"Oh What A night", Endgames/"Miracle In My Heart", Secret Hearts/"Moment of Madness", Alicia Myers/"You Get The Best", Passion Puppets/"ile Dust", Annie G/"Nuclear Love", Jimi Tunnell/"U Turn"", Musical Youth/"She's Trouble", Artist: Various Artists Length: 01:35:46 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.23.mp3, 1.8.1.13.23.wav Note: See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 23)
      - [News] News Scrapbook, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:04:36 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.24.mp3, 1.8.1.13.24.wav (Box 13, Cassette 24)
      - [Newman, Randy] Kate Bush "The Dreaming"and… "Mexican Radio & Walking Voodoo" Randy Newman "Trouble in Paradise"/"Hungry Wolf", Artist: Kate Bush Length: 01:32:34 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.37.mp3, 1.8.1.11.37.wav (Box 11, Cassette 37)
      - [Nixon, Richard] A President Resigns August 8, 1974 President Nixon Resigns Vice-President For Comments President Nixon's Goodbye Gerald Ford- 38th President of the United States Narrated by Bob Hardy Historic Events as Broadcast by KMOX/1120 CBS RADIO "the Voice Of St. Louis", Artist: KMOX Length: 01:05:05 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.9.mp3, 1.8.1.13.9.wav (Box 13, Cassette 9)
      - [Ocasek, Ric] The Cars - Panorama Ric O - Beatitutde, Artist: The Cars Length: 01:33:58 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.1.mp3, 1.8.1.12.1.wav (Box 12, Cassette 1)
      - [Oldies] Oldies, Artist: Oldies Length: 00:55:15 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.25.mp3, 1.8.1.13.25.wav (Box 13, Cassette 25)
      - [Olsson, Nigel] Nigel Olsson epic lc 11/5/80 Lee Ritenouer e/a la 11/6/80\ John Lennon Murder reax, outside dakota, early am 12/9/80, Artist: Nigel Olsson Length: 01:14:44 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.26.mp3, 1.8.1.13.26.wav (Box 13, Cassette 26)
      - [On Record] On Record- CBS Radio 7 recent A&M releases peter bekker (air check quality), Artist: Peter Bekker Length: 00:12:51 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.27.mp3, 1.8.1.13.27.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.17 for cassette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 27)
      - [On Record] Early On Record, Artist: Peter Bekker Length: 00:29:51 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.28.mp3, 1.8.1.13.28.wav (Box 13, Cassette 28)
      - [Paley, William] Interview- William Paley 8/19/77, Artist: William Paley Length: 00:17:40 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.29.mp3, 1.8.1.13.29.wav (Box 13, Cassette 29)
      - [Parker, Graham] Graham Parker (Marble Arch) (High Times) etc. \ Side A: Graham Parker 'Marble Arch': White honey - thats what yhey all say - back door love - Back to school days - Silly-thing - Chain of fools - don’t ask me questions - you cant hurry love - soul shoes - kansas city - I want you back (single) - high times- hold back the night \ Side B (Hightimes) (Howlin Winds): Heat treatment-0 pourin' it about - stick to me - N.Y. Shuffle - H.W. - Lady doctor - Howlin' wind - Between you & Me - Gypsy blood - youve got to be kidding 0 Not if it pleases me - Fools good - watch the moon come down, Artist: Graham Parker Length: 01:01:28 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.30.mp3, 1.8.1.13.30.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.15 for casette J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 30)
      - [Perlman, Itzhak] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, 1:26:54; Artist: Itzhak Perlman Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Pierce, Andy] Patrick Simmons - 4/7/1983 Elektra - la David Bellamy merv griffin theatre Andy Pierce Epic records 4/8 Carl Wilson rogers & cowan 4/12, Artist: Andy Pierce Length: 01:30:39 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.27.mp3, 1.8.1.11.27.wav (Box 11, Cassette 27)
      - [Plant, Robert] Robert Plant/ Sweet Dreams, 1:00:57; Artist: Robert Plant Length: 01:00:57 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.31.mp3, 1.8.1.13.21.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.17 for J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 31)
      - [Plimsouls] Peter Bernstein/Mark Goldenberg Cretones 3/2/81 EA/KA Mark Case- Plimsouls ditto Mark Saffan 3/2/81 EA/LA, Artist: Peter Bernstein Length: 00:01:05 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.28.mp3, 1.8.1.11.28.wav (Box 11, Cassette 28)
      - [Pointer, June] Philip Glass, June Pointer 5/83 NYC. Zappa 6/15/83 CBS-D, Artist: Philip Glass Length: 00:59:09 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.32.mp3, 1.8.1.12.32.wav (Box 12, Cassette 32)
      - [Prince, John] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, Artist: John Prince Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Queen Ida] Clifton Chanier Queen Ida, Artist: Clifton Chanier Length: 01:07:28 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.5.mp3, 1.8.1.12.5.wav (Box 12, Cassette 5)
      - [Raitt, Bonnie] Lorena McKennit/ The Visit/ Bonnie Raitt/Longing In Their Hearts \ A: All Souls Night/Bonny Portmore/Between The Shadows/Lady of Shalott/Greensleeves/Tango To Evora/Covetrard Lullaby/The Old Ways/Cymbeline \B: Love Sneaking Upon You/Longing In Their Hearts/ You/ Cool, Clear Water/Circle Dance/I sho Do/Dimming The Day/Feeling of Falling/Steal Your heart Away/Storm Warning/ Hell To Pay/Shadow and Doubt, Artist: Bonnie Raitt Length: 01:43:07 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.19.mp3, 1.8.1.13.19.wav (Box 13, Cassette 19)
      - [Rameau, Jean-Phillipe] J.P. Rameau / B. James, Artist: Bob James Length: Unknown Type: Unknown Note: Cassette does not play (Box 12, Cassette 44)
      - [Ramos, Bob] Bob Ramos Musea Creative Media 30- Bogardus Place NYC 10040, Artist: Bob Ramos Length: 00:15:14 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.32.mp3, 1.8.1.13.32.wav (Box 13, Cassette 32)
      - [Relativity] Relativity I Relativity (gathering Pace), Artist: Relativity Length: 01:30:19 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.33.mp3, 1.8.1.13.33.wav (Box 13, Cassette 33)
      - [Relativity] Relativity I + II, Artist: Relativity Length: 01:32:00 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.34.mp3, 1.8.1.13.34.wav (Box 13, Cassette 34)
      - [Roche, Maggie and Terre] A) Roche's * Seductive Reasoning Maggie + Terre Roche - Seductive Reasining - Columbia KC 33232 1. Underneath the moon 2. Down the dream 3. Wigglin Man 4. West Virginia 5. If you emptied out all of your pockets you could not make the change 6. Telephone bill 7. Malachy's 8. Burden of proof 9. Mountain People 10. Jill of all trades Margaret Roche (1975), Artist: Maggie and Terre Roche Length: 00:31:34 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.35.mp3, 1.8.1.13.35.wav Note: See folder 1.8.1.6.17 for J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 35)
      - [Roche, Maggie and Terre] Roche's / Jags, Artist: Maggie and Terre Roche Length: 01:37:22 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.36.mp3, 1.8.1.13.36.wav Note: See folder 1.8.1.6.17 for J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 36)
      - [Saint] Saint 1. Some People 2. U Drive Me Crazy 3. I close my eyes, Artist: Saint Length: 00:12:46 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.37.mp3, 1.8.1.13.37.wav Note: See folder 1.8.1.6.17 for J-Card (Box 13, Cassette 37)
      - [Saint] Saint 1) I have a vision 2) Think about me 3) You drive me crazy 4) Cherry Pie 5) Some people 6) Stand and deliver 7) I really want to 8) Bang, Bang baby, Artist: Saint Length: 00:32:29 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.39.mp3, 1.8.1.13.39.wav (Box 13, Cassette 38)
      - [Saint] Saint First Remix, Artist: Sainy Length: 00:10:33 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.1.mp3, 1.8.1.14.1.wav (Box 14, Cassette 1)